{"questions": [{"question": "Give me details of Section 17 in The Indian Contract Act, 1872", "answer": "Various criteria exist for circumstances that amount to fraud, including: When someone declares something as fact that he does not think to be true, then that amounts to fraud. For instance, Mohan is aware that Rohan cheats. However, Mohan tells Priya that Rohan is a trustworthy individual with whom she can conduct business. This is a case of fraud by Mohan. Any behaviour that the law expressly defines as fraudulent.The active concealment of a fact by one having knowledge or belief in the fact. Any other act intended to deceive. A promise made without any intention of performing it. Essential Elements of Fraud The essential elements of fraud are outlined below: The false representation must be made knowingly, or Without the conviction that it is true, or made carelessly without knowledge of its truthfulness."}, {"question": "Power of controller in Section 17 in THE PATENTS ACT, 1970", "answer": "Power of Controller to make orders respecting dating of application (1) Subject to the provisions of section 9, at any time after the filing of an application and before the grant of the patent under this Act, the Controller may, at the request of the applicant made in the prescribed manner, direct that the application shall be post-dated to such date as may be specified in the request, and proceed with the application accordingly: Provided that no application shall be post-dated under this sub-section to a date later than six months from the date on which it was actually made or would, but for the provisions of this sub-section, be deemed to have been made. (2) Where an application or specification (including drawings) or any other document is required   to be amended under section 15, the application or specification or other document shall, if the Controller so directs, be deemed to have been made on the date on which the requirement is complied with or where the application or specification or other document is returned to the applicant on the date on which it is re-filed after complying with the requirement."}, {"question": "Give me details of Section 17 in Indian Registration Act, 1908", "answer": "(1) The following documents shall be registered, if the properties to which they relate is situate in a district in which, and if they have been executed on or after the date on which, Act No. XVI of 1864, of the Indian Registration Act 1866, or the Indian Registration Act 1871, or the Indian Registration Act 1877, or the this Act came or comes into force, namely:- (a) instruments of gift of immoveable property;(b) other non-testamentary instruments which purport or operate to create, declare, assign, limit or extinguish, whether in present or in future, any right, title or interest, whether vested or contingent, of the value of one hundred rupees, and upwards, to or in immoveable property; (c) non-testamentary instruments which acknowledge the receipt or payment of any consideration on account of the creation, declaration, assignment, limitation or extinction of any such right, title or interest; and (d) leases of immoveable property from year to year, or for any term exceeding one year, or reserving a yearly rent;(e) non-testamentary instruments transferring or assigning any decree or order of a court or any award when such decree or order or award purports or operates to create, declare, assign, limit or extinguish, whether in present or in future, any right, title or interest, whether vested or contingent, of the value of one hundred rupees and upwards, to or in immoveable property (Added by Act No. 21 of 1929);"},{"question":"3 or Three directors named as principal perpetrators in satyam fraud case","answer":"They are Byrraju Ramalinga Raju (“Ramalinga Raju”), Byrraju Rama Raju (“Rama Raju”), and Vadlamani Srinivas."},{"question":"Audit Committee members who are charged in satyam fraud case","answer":"Several members of the Company's Audit Committee (“AC Defendants”) are also named in the Class action: Mangalam Srinivasan (“Srinivasan”), Krishna G. Palepu (“Palepu”), M. Rammohan Rao (“Rao”), T.R. Prasad, and V.S. Raju."},{"question":"who were charged against Securities violations act in satyam fraud case","answer":"Securities Act violations have been brought against the following outside directors (“SA Defendants”): Srinivasan, Palepu, Rao, Vinod K. Dham, and Ram Mynampati"},{"question":"who were charged as defendants in satyam fraud case","answer":"Various PricewaterhouseCoopers entities (“PwC Defendants”) provided outside auditing services and are named as defendants: PricewaterhouseCoopers International Ltd., PricewaterhouseCoopers LLP, PriceWaterhouse, PricewaterhouseCoopers Private Ltd., and Lovelock & Lewes."},{"question":"what are the Settlement class in satyam fraud case","answer":"On September 13, 2011, this Court entered judgments settling the Class action as to Satyam and the PwC Defendants and establishing the Settlement Class. (Dkt. Nos. 363, 364.)"},{"question":"what are the Dkt reference in satyam fraud case","answer":"Dkt. Nos. 363, 364."},{"question":"what are the sections violated by Satyam","answer":"violations of sections 10(b) and 20(a) of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 (“Exchange Act”), 15 U.S.C. §§ 78j(b) and 78t(a), SEC Rule 10b–5, 17 C.F.R. § 240.10b–5 (“Rule 10b–5”), and sections 11, 12(a)(2) and 15 of the Securities Act of 1933 (“Securities Act”), 15 U.S.C. §§ 77k, 77 l(a)(2), and 77 o (the “Class action”)"},{"question":"List sections of violations based on Aberdeen","answer":"violations of sections 10(b) and 20(a) of the Exchange Act and Rule 10b–5 and common law claims for fraud, negligence, and negligent misrepresentation (“Aberdeen action”)"},{"question":"IPC/Penal code against which Raju was charged","answer":"Under the Indian Penal Code, 1860, the Raju brothers were charged with criminal breach of trust, cheating, criminal conspiracy, and forgery"},{"question":"Victims of the Satyam fraud case","answer":"Satyam employees, client, shareholders, bankers and also indian government"},{"question":"Factors that constitute a fraud under Section 17 of the Indian Contract Act, 1872","answer":"Establishing facts without being convinced of their accuracy. Fraud is established when it is demonstrated that a false representation was made; either intentionally or unintentionally, without a firm trust in its accuracy, or irresponsibly irresponsible, regardless of whether it is true or not. As a result, the core of fraud is willful deception, which is dealt with in the first three clauses of Section 17.Promise without planning to keep the contractual obligations Section 17 states that the original purpose of not executing the promise made is a required element of fraud and that such an intention cannot be inferred. The fraud anticipated by this provision is one that occurs at the outset of the transaction and does not involve any later activity or representation on the part of the party or their representative. This clause applies to a variety of situations, including, When one party contracts with another without the intent to perform in order to prevent the other from contracting with a third party, Contracting without the intent to pay the agreed consideration, and One party promises the other something that he or she is certain he or she will not be able to accomplish within the contractual period. Active concealment"},{"question":"Factors that contributed to the Satyam fraud case","answer":"Greed. Ambitious corporate growth.Deceptive reporting practices, lack of transparency.Excessive interest in maintaining stock prices.Executive incentives.Stock market expectations.Nature of accounting rules.ESOPs issued to those whoprepared fake bills.High-risk deals that went sour.Audit failures (both Internal & External).Theaggressiveness of investment banks, commercial banks,.Rating agencies & investors.WeakIndependentdirectors and Audit committee.Whistle Whistleblower policy not being effective."}]}